Contact

attri2707@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anjalisingh-947ab0179 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language) Html/css

React Native

Certifications

Software Engineering Virtual Experience

Python

English Proficiency

Pre- Qualifier

Honors-Awards

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador

Anjali Singh

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador at Microsoft New Delhi

Summary

Experienced Technical Content Writer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology. Skilled in React, React Native, Android Development, and HTML. Strong media and communication professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused on Hons from Galgotias University.

Experience

Microsoft
Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador
August 2020 - Present (1 month)

Edulyt India
Data Analytics Intern
May 2020 - June 2020 (2 months)

IncludeHelp
Technical Content Writer
October 2019 - February 2020 (5 months)

Check my articles at https://www.includehelp.com/Members/Anjali-Singh.aspx

WeIntern Internship under operations March 2019 - April 2019 (2 months)

Education

Galgotias University
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, hons · (2017 - 2021)

Kendriya Vidyalaya PCM · (2016 - 2017)